Ano-chan karuta
I thought I'd make an ano-chan karuta for this project.
Anouki, the dog, also hits a stick
I'd like you to think about what it would be like to be Anochan.
First of all, please draw the karuta cards that have been prepared for you.
If you draw a picture that comes to mind...
Randomly?
Yes.
Then, draw a picture here and there. Randomly from among these. Yes. There you go.
Huh?
Ha-ha-ha.
What?
You can't get lucky.
You're lucky I don't write about luck. This is the short version of the channel.
I'll just keep pulling.
I wonder what this is.
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
So, do you want me to write a curry for M?
Yes, I'll go then. Mu.
What is it?
Gather around at Muji and see if you can find it. Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's like this.
Organic life
I buy houseplants I don't know, all the time.
I buy cotton towels, etc.
It's a good thing.
Yes!
Hey, Ano.
What's up?
I have a question. Is this a good time?
Yeah, sure.
My allowance is lower than everyone else's.
How can I get my parents to give it to me?
Money can't buy you a future.
If you don't have more allowance than everyone else.
Why don't you make more memories than everyone else?
Thank you very much.
Whose question was that?
The first word is accident, accident, accident.
Make up an association with
Well, an accident is a happening, right?
Yes, like an accident.
Accident
Accident is a story about a human being trying to save a human being,
An Accident is a story about a man saving a man. Yes, yes, accidents.
It's ready.
Pink dumplings.
I like Chinese food.
So I order the dumplings, and they're all pink inside. Pink? Pink? Pink? Pink?
Pink?
Pink? Pink? Pink? Like pink-pink. Like pink-pink.
But I said, "Pink, pink, pink.
I said, "This is pink color.
They said, "OK," and went back and made a new one.
And this is what came out, so I was scared.
I ate only the skin.
This is a recent accident.
I'm sure you'll learn a lot from it.
Amachannel, please subscribe to our channel!